No way, impossible!
This isn't real.
How did you do that?
Whoa, what the?
He finished before you started.
That's so lame.
How weird.
What's going on with him?
Shino!
Spirits.
Special designation disaster beings that exist in a critical space.
Approach one, annihilate them by military force.
Approach two, date them and make them fall in love.
Thank you.
See you next time.
Like with lips?
It'll open the path for spirit power to flow.
There's just one problem.
Your deadline is 12 tonight.
So you're saying that by midnight...
We all have to kiss Shido?
I can think of worse things than having to kiss Shido to save his life.
Commander, bad news.
Shido seems to escape from the infirmary.
Is that Shido Itsuka?
A woman?
Right.
A woman.
Gotta make her fall for me.
Can't forget to do my duty.
Man, I've missed you so much, Alan.
What in the actual heck happened here?
You don't think Shido did this?
Wonder.
Such spirit power.
Luckily, we can track where he is with the monitor.
Gani, let's go.
I don't get it.
How are you doing this?
You're in my territory, after all.
Don't be hostile, my dear.
Okay?
I just want us to understand one another.
You jerk!
If you think this is funny, you're wrong.
I'm not joking, though.
Who cares if we're from different sides?
We can still love one another, right?
Helen, it's you I want.
You've officially gone too far!
Look, don't be difficult, okay?
See ya.
Till we meet again.
Ciao.
That's so humiliating!
You'll pay for this someday, I swear it!
Cool.
My body feels as light as a feather.
What a great day.
Everyone's power is surging inside me,
and I feel like I could sing!
I love you.
I want you.
I need you.
The sky is blue,
and my heart is clear and bright.
Shido!
Oh, hey, Toka.
Coterie, everyone.
To what do I owe this pleasure, huh?
Listen up, lover boy.
We're here to save your dumbass.
To save me?
Seriously?
You found me so you can kiss me?
That's right, and mine's gonna be a big old passionate smooch!
All right, then.
Though I have a feeling I'm gonna miss all this power.
I'll do it, on one condition.
What's with that smirk?
Listening.
Come on, let's hear it, then.
Before, I had to get each one of you to fall for me in order to seal your powers, right?
But this time, you have to make me fall for you.
We do?
I'll just be honest, though.
I already like all of you girls plenty as it is.
So to say you have to make me fall for you isn't the most accurate.
Use any method you want, but make sure my heart skips a beat.
Just enough that I can't wait to give you a big kiss.
Cool?
Right, make his heart skips a beat. Got it.
And make it good, so that he'll want a kiss.
So be it.
Get ready. Ratataskura's gonna go all out to make you fall for us.
I'm honored.
I'm ready to start whenever you are.
Let's get going real soon.
And begin our date.
Our deadline is midnight tonight, so let's not waste time.
Shido.
Huh. Nice.
Let's see what you've got, ladies.
Hello!
Oh, good, you're here.
Darling!
You look great. All of you.
You went and picked out swimsuits just for me?
I appreciate it.
Well, yeah. I mean, of course we did.
Caution.
It sounds like you're falling for him now.
It's Shido's turn this time around.
What? I know that, okay?
Ratataskura presents...
It's the one and only heart-brabbing falling loveteen!
What?
No.
If you would, allow me to explain the rules.
The spirits will go one at a time, each trying to make Shido's hearts give a beat in their own erotic way.
While that happens, we will, of course, be closely monitoring Shido's excitement level here in the control room.
And once you've inspired him to exceed a certain level...
You'll hear fanfare like this, which indicates a clear triumph.
Please know that the actual kissing of Shido will occur after everyone has completed their turn.
As you know, the deadline is 12 o'clock tonight.
Is all of that clear?
Cut it down!
Listen, I want to get one thing straight before we start.
This isn't the time to screw around with our choices, got it?
Of course not, Commander.
Your lowly, unworthy dog, Kiyohe Kanazuki, will surmount dear Shido's defenses no matter what it takes!
Okay, that wording kind of creeps me out.
I have something I'd like to say.
If we're using a beach anyway, I don't understand why we didn't choose a nudist one like I originally suggested.
Because it's scary!
But if our main goal is to get Shido excited, it'd be a lot more effective to catch him off guard.
Just think about it.
If everyone was naked, we would have already heard that fanfare by now.
Look, that might be true, but there are lines I'm not willing to cross, and this is one of them!
Well, I get what you're saying, Origami.
I feel like that might have the opposite effect.
His shock might actually exceed his excitement.
I see.
Guess I'll strip bit by bit then.
That's the way to do it!
I'd argue there are many ways to proceed.
Origami and the Vice Commander, they make a pretty good team.
Yeah, it seems like they're always on the same wavelength, doesn't it?
Must be all those hobbies they both share.
Everyone ready?
Then let's get this conquest of Shido underway!
Do we have any volunteers to go first?
Duh!
A true warrior is always the first to get to a battle.
Now let's get this ball rolling!
Honor, Kaguya and I can get this done.
All right!
The Yamai sisters are first up to bat!
That's the hurricane children for you, rushing ahead fiercely like the wind!
Two girls at once, huh?
Be gentle with me, okay?
Kaguya.
Yuzuru.
Sure, but prepare yourself!
You're about to fall for us so hard, dude!
There's no doubt.
A knockout in a single round.
Here we go, everyone.
Please make your choice.
Huh.
Should it be one or two?
Huh?
Why would you ignore option three?
Just do it!
Strap a rope around his neck like rain!
It's the only way!
You hear me?
You have to go with option three and right!
She don't let you go!
Uh, guys?
What are you doing?
Coup d'etat?
Revenution?
The commander left orders to tie you up if you started screwing around!
Oh, what a commander.
In that case, you can tie me up tighter.
What's wrong with you?
The left side is way too slack.
What does that idiot even think he's doing?
I guess that means it'll be number two or the squeeze attack,
which is no big shocker, if we're honest.
So, hey guys.
What's going on?
What do you think?
Like it, Shido?
Don't our feminine charms make your heart go aflutter?
Agreement.
It's no point in trying to lie to yourself, you know.
Feel.
See?
Of course, what guy wouldn't like it,
but it's a little much with both of you at once.
I can't really focus.
What?
Dumbfounded.
Shido doesn't seem fazed in the slightest.
But hey, thanks anyway.
You're putting so much thought into this.
I want you to know I appreciate it.
Wait.
We've failed?
Embarrassment.
And I feel cheated for some reason.
Wait.
Cheer up, girls.
Appearances can be deceiving.
He may look composed, but his excitement level's climbing.
Try choice two this time.
What gives?
You only got ice cream for yourselves?
Not gonna lie, I'm kind of bummed out.
That's a hasty conclusion, Shido.
Bestow.
One of these ice creams is all for you.
One will be plenty for us.
We're used to sharing things.
Oh, well, thank you.
So sweet.
I can't get enough.
Sorry to interrupt,
but weren't you supposed to be doing that with Shin
and not with each other?
What?
Awkward.
Now that you mention it.
Oops.
Uh-oh.
It's so cold.
Uh.
Yes.
Today's very first fanfare.
Yeah, my sisters.
You made that boy fall for you hard.
He's not kidding.
You two really got me good.
So, next is Natsumi, right?
You volunteered to go next all on your own?
Thank you for that.
Are you kidding?
The rest of us drew straws.
This condition of yours is absurd.
The others might be able to manage this,
but to make you fall for me?
It's not even possible.
That's definitely not true.
You're plenty cute, Natsumi.
I can't do this now.
Hold on a sec.
Hmm?
Hey, let's play some multiplayer, huh?
Okay, sure.
Wait, but Natsumi doesn't even own the game, does she?
Nah, then she can just play by herself.
How dare they?
You chose that game on purpose, you jerks!
Huh.
Now I've got him in the bag for sure.
Natsumi, it's dangerous to use spirit power right now.
Revert back to your other form.
It'll be fine.
I'm in a real swimsuit and everything.
My guess is he'll fall for me within a minute.
Sorry you had to wait.
Worth it, though.
Natsumi, you look incredible.
Well, thanks, sweet boy.
I can't blame you for being interested in a big girl's body.
Another success!
Natsumi's baggy suit and Shido's pervy barn for the win!
Seriously?
Yoshino, what's that?
Oh, don't worry.
It's nothing, right, Yoshino?
Yoshino scores a success!
Wow, look at this.
It is quite a shift in mood.
I thought you might be bored of the beat.
From now on, it's adult time.
Elegant, grown-up time.
They say that boys grow fast, if I'm not mistaken.
But a woman can change the very moment you look away.
Know what I mean, dear big brother?
That's my commander!
Success!
Darling, I'm so glad I found you here.
Tonight, I'm gonna sing a song just for you.
Neku, success!
What?
I didn't have a chance to perform my song!
Hey, I heard that you were up next.
Yes, that's right.
I'm not gonna drink, okay?
No problem.
Alcohol-free.
Something the matter?
I don't know anymore.
Don't know what?
It doesn't matter.
Cheers!
That's definitely alcohol-free.
What's wrong?
You okay?
Oh, Itsuka.
How is it you managed to be so handsome anyway?
Itsuka?
Hold on.
Are you that origami?
I mean, does it really make a difference to you?
Whenever I spend time thinking about you, I get all warm and tingly inside, and my heart
seems to get all full and tight.
I-Itsuka, I love you so much that I hardly even know what to do.
Origami, susu!
Well, that's seven of us, clear.
It's just Toka now.
Something wrong?
No.
It's just that when I heard Origami talking about how much she loves Shido, I felt my chest clenching
up right here.
I know saving Shido should be my priority, but...
I'm having a pretty hard time letting go of this feeling.
These silly thoughts keep getting in the way.
I don't think that's a silly thought at all, though, Toka.
Yeah, it's probably the most important emotion you'll rely on to save Shido.
I don't understand.
It's scary.
Go on.
We're counting on you, okay?
Right.
It feels so weird.
Why, though?
Origami said that drink was non-alcoholic.
Sorry to make you wait!
Ta-da!
Oh, wow.
That looks really good.
Well, I just figured you might be hungry.
So I brought every tasty food I could find with me.
Shall we begin?
Sure, yeah.
Thank you.
Shido!
Shido, what?
What's going on?
He okay?
No.
It happened sooner than we thought.
Are you all right, Shido?
Stay with us!
Get away, Toka!
Flashing thunder wave!
Shido!
There are abnormal spirit waste practically pouring out of him!
His spirit powers are totally off the charts!
His emotion readings don't make any sense!
He's on a rampage!
Spacial quake alarm!
Full danger!
At this rate, we'll have an even worse disaster than the one we had 30 years ago!
Coterie!
What are you doing?
We need to stop him!
Panic mode.
It's officially a race against time.
All right, then.
Looks like it's up to me.
The Tadasker made Don Sleuth specifically because of this risk, so we could eliminate Shido if we needed to.
I'm so sorry, Big Brother.
Forgive me for having no other choice but this.
What are you doing?
You must never use this, Coterie.
We'll find another way, together.
I agree with Origami.
You're not alone, Coterie.
There's Origami and me.
Kaguya and Yuzuru.
Yoshino, Miku, and Natsumi, too.
If we all put our powers together, I'm sure that we can save Shido.
Toka.
Origami.
If we don't slow Shido down somehow, we're never gonna catch up!
Is that even possible, though?
What can we do?
I can be so whimsical sometimes, can't I?
What happened?
This is our chance!
Yeah, I doubt we'll have long to make it count.
Relax.
It's plenty of time for the Yamai sisters.
Raphael Al-Ra'em!
Response.
Raphael Al-Nahal!
Shido, we're here to help you.
Grateful.
After all, you're the one who saved us first, so now it's our turn.
It'll be over soon.
Please hang on.
There.
Are you happy now?
Aw, you didn't even try to make it a good one.
Now I've shared an indirect kiss with Natsumi.
Come on now.
Metatron!
Rotary!
Big brother!
I'm sorry!
Shido!
I am your final opponent!
Oh my gosh!
We're out of time!
Hurry!
Where'd her power go?
Taka!
Stay back!
Don't worry.
And don't interfere.
I feel like it's important for me to do this on my own.
Oh, Shido.
Is it possible that you've had to fight against this kind of pain and fear the entire time?
How did you stay strong?
How were you able to keep reaching out through so much chaos to save us all?
Oh, now I see.
I think this must be the feeling everyone calls love.
But it's different from how I feel for the others.
It's a love that's only for Shido.
That's why.
Shido, I'm here.
Hol Oooh
When you know my soul of ingrained tears
You have a scarlet man
Killer from us
Huge
f
Hey, Tocca
sure you don't want me to do that no thanks this is important i'm the only one who didn't get you
to fall for me and so toka all done shiro tasty right yeah it is did it work did your heart skip
a beat you know it totally did
you